A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Second Auditor - Literary Fund Records, 1785-1927
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia. Office of the Second Auditor. Literary Fund Records, 1785-1927
The Library of Virginia
SAI 30
12 cu. ft. (25 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Second Auditor.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transfer information unknown.
Biographical Information
The history of the second auditor's office began in 1823 when the office was created by the General Assembly as part of an act to improve the navigation of the James and Kanawha rivers. Under the act, the second auditor was given responsibility for the Fund for Internal Improvements and for acting as secretary to the Board of Public Works. He was also appointed clerk and accountant to the directors of the Literary Fund. An act passed in 1829 made him the superintendent of the fund, and he assumed the responsibilities formerly held by the president and directors. In 1835 an act authorized the commissioners of the newly created Sinking Fund to redeem the state's debt, and the second auditor was appointed a commissioner with the responsibility, together with the state treasurer, for keeping the accounts of this fund.
Prior to the Civil War, the duties of the second auditor were fairly simple and straightforward, as were the duties of the treasurer. After the war, however, the devastation of the state's economy resulted in the creation of more numerous and complicated records concerning the redemption of the state debt. The office of the second auditor suffered from inadequate procedures for maintaining accurate records on the state's finances. By 1874, neither office had a complete or accurate account of the public debt, and between 1874 and 1877 major scandals were disclosed involving both offices and that of the sergeant at arms of the House of Delegates. Although a complete revision of the accounting methods used by both financial offices, especially the second auditor's, was called for, only minor changes were made.
In 1906 a legislative committee made periodic inspections of the finance offices. Finding that the situation in the second auditor's office remained almost as chaotic as it had been in 1874, the committee recommended that the office be abolished and its duties taken over by the first auditor. Although the committee's recommendations were not followed, its members continued to call for reform. Action was taken only after the election of Governor Harry F. Byrd, Sr., in 1926. Byrd hired a group of consultants from New York to study the finance offices, and the resulting report brought about a complete reorganization of state government in 1928. The offices of first and second auditor were abolished and replaced by a newly created office of comptroller. The second auditor's office closed its books on February 29, 1928.
The Literary Fund, which is still in existence, was established by an act passed by the General Assembly on 12 February 1811. Revenues derived from fines (except militia fines) and the sale of land escheated for unpaid taxes were deposited in the Literary Fund and the money was used to build schools and educate the state's poor children. The Fund provides services such as low-interest loans for school construction, grants under the interest rate subsidy program, debt service for technology funding, and support for the state's share of teacher retirement required by the Standards of Quality. The responsibility for keeping the accounts of the Literary Fund was shifted from the auditor to the second auditor when the latter office was created on 24 February 1823.
Scope and Content
Records, 1785-1927, including accounts, bonds, clippings, correspondence, court records, deeds, forms, lists, minutes, reports, treasurer receipts, and vouchers of the Second Auditor Literary Fund. This collection provides a broad overview of how the monies were collected and spent throughout the Commonwealth to support education for the state's poor children. Also as the Literary Fund was financed by money from fines, land and property forfeitures, penalties, confiscations, and escheats, this collection documents the financial histories of Virginians across various localities.
The correspondence, 1811-1927 (bulk 1811-1862 and 1903-1914), is arranged chronologically into eight boxes. The correspondence, 1811-1862, includes letters from people who were appointed as agents for the Literary Fund; counties asking for loans to build schools; requests for copies of legislation; and payments of debt, among other topics. Of note is the correspondence, 1833-1842, relating to the estate of Burk[e] Freeman and Adam Waterford, free men of Washington County, Virginia. At issue was whether a slave can inherit from an estate or whether the money from his estate would go to the Literary Fund. Also of note are letters, 10 April and 13 August 1820, from Thomas Jefferson, regarding funds sent to the University of Virginia from the Literary Fund. There is also a drawing of an addition to the University of Virginia gymnasium, 1835, located in the Correspondence, Schools, University of Virginia.
The Correspondence, Schools, 1835-1853, includes information on money that was sent to schools and academies across Virginia and is arranged alphabetically by school name. Included are accounts, annual reports, bonds for teachers, minutes, and resolutions. Many local academies were included as well as some colleges and universities such as the Medical College of Richmond, University of Virginia, and Virginia Military Institute, among others. The correspondence, 1903-1914, relates to salaries of superintendants; repayment of loans schools had taken; submitting money the county had gathered for teacher pensions/retired teachers fund; asking for copies of school insurance policies; investment of literary funds into bonds and stock; and correspondence to and from the Second Auditor.
Included are deeds, 1816-1847, for the sale of James River Company shares to the Literary Fund. Also included are papers relating to escheated lands, 1785-1851, including correspondence, court records, deeds, reports, and wills regarding land that was sold with the proceeds going to the Literary Fund. The deeds and escheated lands records contain some useful genealogical information. Included are lists of academies to which surplus quotas have been appropriated and lists of fines collected by counties.
Included are papers, 1884-1927, relating to the Miller Manual Labor School in Albemarle County, Virginia. The Miller School is one of several legacies of Samuel Miller, a native of Albemarle County who grew up in poverty but went on to become a wealthy investor in Lynchburg. He established The Miller School in Albemarle County to provide a first-rate education for children from Albemarle County and the surrounding area, regardless of financial condition. Included are accounts, clippings, correspondence, receipts, and reports. Also included are Lists of fines and penalties returned as insolvents, 1810-1822, which contain oversize forms listing the defendants names, amount, and date of judgments. These are only available for a few counties.
The Reports, School Superintendents and Boards of School Commissioners, 1860-1868, contain forms detailing annual expenditures spent on tuition, books, clerks, number of schools and children, and school salaries, per county. Also included are bonds for those appointed superintendent of schools; annual reports; and accounts and finances. Some of the annual reports list teachers names and number of students and what courses were taught.
Also included are treasurers receipts, 1823-1863, containing the names of people paying fines and why, sent in from local county authorities (such as the clerk, sheriff, or treasurer). The vouchers for warrants, 1823-1857, include bonds, payments made to presidents and directors of the literary fund, and payments made to counties (also the University of Virginia) for the amount of surplus school quota due.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title, with oversized materials arranged to the rear.
Contents List
- Accounts, 1840-1857 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Accounts, Library Fund, 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Accounts, 1907-1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Accounts, State Institutions of Higher Education, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bonds, Free schools, 1856-1857 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bonds, 1861-1863 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Census statistics, 1840 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1811 July 5-18 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1811 July 20-30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1811 August (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1811 September-December (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1812 January-June (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1812 July-December (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1813 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1814 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1814 May (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1814 June-1816 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1817 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1818-1819 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1820-1821 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Insolvents and Fines from County Attorneys, 1820-1821 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1822 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, Estate of Burk Freeman and Adam Waterford (free men), Washington County, Va., 1833-1842 (Box 2, Folder 9a)
- Correspondence, Schools, Berryville Academy (Clarke County, Va.), 1838-1839 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, Schools, Botetourt Seminary (Botetourt County, Va.), 1841 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Schools, Brooke Academy (Brooke County, Va.), 1837-1847 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, Schools, Emory and Henry College (Washington County, Va.), 1846 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, Schools, Fox Hill Academy (Elizabeth City County, Va.), 1835-1846 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, Schools, Fredericksburg Academy, 1841-1850 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, Schools, Halifax Academy (Halifax County, Va.), 1838 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Schools, Halls Free School (Hanover County, Va.), 1847 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Schools, Hampden Sidney College Medical Dept. (Richmond, Va.), 1850-1851 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, Schools, Hampton Academy (Elizabeth City County, Va.), 1837 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, Schools, Lewisburg Academy (Greenbrier County, Va.), 1840-1847 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Schools, Marshall Academy (Cabell County, Va.), 1838-1846 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Schools, Martinsburg Academy (Berkeley County, Va.), 1839-1841 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Schools, Mathews Academy (Mathews County, Va.), 1846 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, Schools, Margaret Academy (Accomack County, Va.), 1836 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, Schools, Medical College of Richmond, 1844-1848 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Schools, Medical College of Winchester, 1848-1849 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, Schools, Mercer Academy (Kanawha County, Va.), 1840-1842 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, Schools, New Market Academy (Shenandoah County, Va.), 1841 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, Schools, Norfolk Academy, 1836-1851 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, Schools, Northumberland Academy, 1836-1841 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, Schools, North Western Academy (Harrison County, Va.), 1846-1852 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, Schools, Randolph Macon College (Mecklenburg County, Va.), 1830-1847 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, Schools, Richmond City Academy, 1843 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, Schools, Romney Classical Institute (Hampshire County, Va.), 1850 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, Schools, Salem Academy (Roanoke, Va.), 1834 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, Schools, Staunton Academy (Augusta County, Va.), 1836-1841 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, Schools, St. Brides Academy (Norfolk County, Va.), 1839-1847 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, Schools, Strasburg Academy (Shenandoah County, Va.), 1846 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, Schools, Suffolk Academy, 1837 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, Schools, University of Virginia (Albemarle County, Va.), 1835 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, Schools, Virginia Military Institute (Lexington, Va.), 1842-1850 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, Schools, Washington Henry Academy (Westmoreland County, Va.), 1837-1841 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, Schools, Washington College (Lexington, Va.), 1841-1852 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, Martin Dawson Fund, 1853-1857 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1854 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1856 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1857 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1858 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1859 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1860 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1882-1901 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1903-1907 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1908 January-June (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1908 July-September (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1908 October (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1908 November-December (Box 4, Folder 11a)
- Correspondence, 1909-1910 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1911 January-March (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1911 April (Box 5, Folder 1a)
- Correspondence, 1911 May-June (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1911 July-August (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1911 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1911 October 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1911 October 16-31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1911 November (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1911 December (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Insurance, 1911-1912 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1912 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1912 February-March (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1912 April (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1912 May-June (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1912 July-August (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1912 September (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1912 October 1-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1912 October 15-31 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1912 November (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1912 December (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Stock, 1913-1919 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1913 January (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1913 February-March (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1913 April (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1913 May (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1913 June (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1913 July (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1913 August (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1913 September (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1913 October-November (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1913 December (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1914 January (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1914 February-March (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1916-1927 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Deeds, Shares of James River Company, 1816-1819 March (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Deeds, Shares of James River Company, 1819 April-October (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Deeds, Shares of James River Company, 1820-1822 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Deeds, Shares of James River Company, 1824-1830 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Deeds, Shares of James River Company, 1835-1847 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Escheated Lands, Bath-Halifax Counties, 1829-1849 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Escheated Lands, Halifax-Pendleton Counties, 1822-1851 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Escheated Lands, Bristoe Estate (Prince William Co., Va.), 1820-1833 (Box 9, Folder 4a)
- Escheated Lands, Pendleton County-Richmond, 1790-1842 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Escheated Lands, Staunton-Wood County, 1825-1846 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Escheated Lands, Wood County, 1785-1823 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- List of academics and surplus quotas, 1836-1841 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Lists of insolvents and fines, 1810-1822 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miller Manual Labor School, Correspondence, 1884-1914 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Miller Manual Labor School, Receipts, 1890-1900 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Miller Manual Labor School, Reports, 1904-1927 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Monthly salaries of superintendents, ca. 1900 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Order, James City County, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Reports, Annual Expenditures, Accomack-Morgan Counties, 1855-1856 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Reports, Annual Expenditures, Nansemond-York Counties, 1855-1856 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Dinwiddie-King George County, 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Lancaster-Lunenburg County, 1860 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Madison-Mason County, 1860-1862 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Mecklenburg-Morgan County, 1860-1862 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Northampton-Upshur County, 1860-1868 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Reports, School Superintendents and Board of School Commissioners, Warren-Wythe County, 1859-1860 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Resolution, 1821 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, No. 1-20, 1823 March-April (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, No. 21-40, 1823 April-June (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, No. 41-49, 1823 June (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, No. 50-59, 1823 June-July (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, No. 60-71, 1823 July-September (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1823 October-December (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1824 January-September (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1824 October-December (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1825 January-May (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, 1825 June-September (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, 1825 October-December (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, 1826 January-May (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1826 June-September (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1827 October-November (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1827 December (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1828 January-April (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, 1828 May-July (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, 1829 October-December (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, 1830 January-September (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1831 October-December (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1832 January-December (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1843 October-December (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1844 January-April (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, 1844 May-September (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, 1844 October-December (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1845 January-April (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1845 May-December (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1846 January-April (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1846 May-September (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, 1846 October-December (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Treasurers receipts, 1847 January-May (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, 1847 June-December (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, 1848 January-June (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1848 July-December (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1849 January-September (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1850 October-December (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1851 January-May (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, 1851 June-September (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Treasurers receipts, 1851 October-December (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Treasurers receipts, 1852 January-April (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Treasurers receipts, 1852 May-August (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Treasurers receipts, 1852 October-December (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Treasurers receipts, 1853 January-March (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Treasurers receipts, 1853 April-September (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Treasurers receipts, 1862 March-December (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Treasurers receipts, 1863 January-March (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-20, 1823 March-April (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 21-41, 1823 April-June (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 42-58, 1823 July-September (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 213-237, 1824 October-December (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 238-270, 1825 January (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 271-300, 1825 January-February (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 301-328, 1825 February-April (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 240-273, 1825 May-September (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-30, 1828 October-1829 January (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 31-60, 1829 January-February (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 61-80 1829 February-March (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-110, 1829 April-May (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 111-138, 1829 May-September (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-30, 1829 October-1830 January (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 31-60, 1830 January-February (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 61-80, 1830 February-March (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-110, 1830 March-June (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 111-126, 1830 June-September (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-40, 1830 October-1831 January (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 41-80, 1831 January-April (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-100, 1831 April-May (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 101-123, 1831 May-September (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-29, 1832 October-December (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 30-50, 1833 January (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 51-80 1833 January-February (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-110, 1833 February-April (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 111-146, 1833 April-September (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 147-151; No. 5-20, 1833 October-December (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 21-60, 1834 January (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 61-80, 1834 February (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-100, 1833 October-1834 March (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 101-120, 1834 March-May (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 121-152, 1834 May-September (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 130-155, 1844 February (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 156-180, 1844 February-April (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 181-200, 1844 April-July (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 201-218, 1844 July-September (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 21-50, 1856 October (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 51-80, 1856 October (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 1-20, 1856 October (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 81-100, 1856 October (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 101-120, 1856 October (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 121-135, 1856 October-November (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 136-155, 1856 November-December (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 156-180, 1857 January (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 181-200, 1857 January (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 201-225, 1857 January-February (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 226-250, 1857 February (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 251-270, 1857 February-March (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Vouchers for warrants, No. 271-300, 1857 March-April (Box 24, Folder 5)